# You can initializae important data at the top of the page 
score = 0
trivia = { "q": "question", "a": "correct answer", "options": ["choice a", "choice b", "choice c", "choice d", "choice e", "choice f"]},

trivia = [
    { 
     "question": "How many presidents were born in Virginia?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8, 11]
     },
    { "question": "How many presidents were born in New York?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 10]
     },
    { "question": "How many presidents were born in Ohio?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8]
     },
    { "question": "How many presidents were born in Texas?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8]
     },
    { "question": "How many presidents were born in Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [0, 1, 2, 5, 7, 8]
     },
    { "question": "How many presidents were born in Vermont?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [0, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8, 9]
     },
    { "question": "How many presidents were born in Iowa?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [0, 1, 4, 5, 7, 9]
     },
    { "question": "How many presidents were born in Illinois?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [1, 3, 4, 6, 7, 8]
     },
    { "question": "How many presidents were born in Massachussets?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 9]
     },
    { "question": "How many presidents were born in North Carolina?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 8]
     }
]



def main():
    print("Let's play ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ US Presidents ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ Trivia!! ")


if __name__ == "__main__":
    main()
